fairview.org 2017-06-06

# Privacy Statement - Fairview Health Services - Fairview Health Services

We respect your privacy _  
This privacy statement applies to information shared through this website.  
_  
Fairview is concerned about the privacy interests of consumers and is committed to respecting your privacy by using any personal information gathered in only the most responsible way possible. Fairview does not acquire any more information about customers than is necessary to provide efficient and secure service. When we collect personal data, we will endeavor to disclose to you how we will use this information. Fairview will also seek to take all appropriate steps to ensure that any personal information given is protected by secure technology, including using digital signatures and other credit card data protection technology. When Fairview collects your personal data, we may use it for research or to improve our service or website. We will ask if you want us or any of our business partners to use that information to contact you in the future about new products or services that might interest you. If you do not wish to be contacted by Fairview or any of our business partners, you can choose to have your information kept out. Fairview gives access to personal information about consumers only to employees who require it to perform their jobs. We will take every appropriate step to keep your information secure from other employees. If you have questions about this privacy policy, please send an e-mail to the [Fairview web team](https://sslforms.fairview.org/webresponseform.asp).

Notice of Privacy Practices  
These notices describe how health information about you may be used and disclosed and how you can obtain access to this information.

Please call the Fairview privacy office if you have questions about these notices:  
 **612-672-5647**

Fairview Health Services (List of entities)

If you have any questions about these notices, please call the Fairview privacy office at  
612-672-5647.

See also our Legal Notice Statement.
